Discover how little you know about the people you know.
Men, Women & Children is a drama, comedy film directed by Jason Reitman.
Follows the story of a group of high school teenagers and their parents as they attempt to navigate the many ways the
internet has changed their relationships, their communication, their self-image, and their love lives.
Don Truby, played by Adam Sandler.
Patricia Beltmeyer, played by Jennifer Garner.
Helen Truby, played by Rosemarie DeWitt.
Donna Clint, played by Judy Greer.
Kent Mooney, played by Dean Norris.
Narrator (voice), played by Emma Thompson.
Men, Women & Children is a 2014 American comedy-drama film directed by Jason Reitman and co-written with Erin Cressida
Wilson, based on a novel of the same name written by Chad Kultgen that deals with online addiction.
The film stars Rosemarie DeWitt, Jennifer Garner, Judy Greer, Dean Norris, Adam Sandler,
Ansel Elgort, Kaitlyn Dever, and Timothée Chalamet in his film debut.
The film premiered at the 2014 Toronto International
Film Festival on September 6, 2014.
The film was released on October 3, 2014, by Paramount Pictures, and
received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film was a box office bomb, grossing $2.2
million against a $16 million budget.
The film explores themes of high school, overprotective parent, self image.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.